Finding aid for Bentley Historical Library records, 1919 - 2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Division Records
  - Access and Reference Services, 1961-2000
    - Reference Archivist's Office, 1961-2000
      - Nancy Bartlett
        - Cultural Heritage Initiative for Community Outreach (CHICO), 1998 (Box 26)
        - Eastern Michigan University, HIS 479 Workshop in Michigan History, 1987-1993; 8 folders (Box 26)
        - French Visiting Archivists, Ecole Nationale du Patrimoine, 1992-1999 (Box 27)
        - Medical History Topics, 1990 (Box 27)
        - Medical Theses Microfilming, 1992 (Box 27)
        - Microfilm/Microfiche Reader and Printer, 1988-1991 (Box 27)
        - MIRLYN Online Catalog, 1993-1998 (Box 27)
        - MIRLYN Training for Staff, 1995-1997 (Box 27)
        - Networked Information Services Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 27)
        - Paging Key, 1989 (Box 27)
        - Photograph Retreat, 1990 (Box 27)
        - Photograph Operation, 1994-2000 (Box 27)
        - Poetry Here and Then Project (ENG 240 Introduction to Poetry), 1995-1999; 2 folders (Box 27)
        - Policies and Procedures, 1985-1990 (Box 27)
        - Re-cataloging of Photographs, 1986 (Box 27)
        - Research Topics based on Sources at the Bentley Historical Library, 1989-2002 (Box 27)
        - Restricted Collections Policies, 1987 (Box 27)
        - Review of Mary Jo Pugh's Society of American Archivist's Reference Guide, 1988-1989 (Box 27)
        - RLG and RLIN, 1986-1998 (Box 27)
        - Saturday Reference Guide, 1996 (Box 27)
        - Staff, 1973-1995 (Box 27)
        - Students on Site Project, Broadway Bridge, Arts of Citizenship Program, 1997-1998 (Box 27)
        - Trends in Reference, 1989 (Box 27)
        - University of Michigan Master Planning, Venturi, Scott, and Brown, 1997-1998 (Box 27)
        - Vertical File Changes, 1989-1990 (Box 27)
        - Workshop in Reference for Bentley Staff, 1989 (Box 27)
      - Kathy Marquis
        - Affirmative Action Lawsuit, 2000 (Box 27)
        - Medical School Timeline, 1999 (Box 27)
        - Offsite Storage Facilities, 1999-2000 (Box 27)
        - Policies and Procedures, circa 1980-1990 (Box 27)
        - Reference Announcements and Meetings, 1999-2000 (Box 27)
        - Reference Manual, 1985-1999 (Box 27)
        - Student Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 27)
    - Reference Division Reports, 1969-1998
      Tthe Reference Reports subseries consistst of a variety of monthly and annual reports on the division's activities. The early years of reference are shown through the Work Reports. Research topics, user statistics, sample questions, reproduction requests, and annual studies were carefully documented. The Work Report format split into Monthly Reports and Annual Reports in the mid-1980s although generally contain the same type of information. The reports clearly track reference trends and use through the library's history.
      - Work Reports, 1969/1970-1979/1980, 11 folders (Box 27)
      - Work Reports, 1980/1981-1983/1984, 4 folders (Box 28)
      - Monthly Reports, 1985/1986-1997/1998, 13 folders (Box 28)
      - Quarterly Reference Reports, 1985-1989 (Box 28)
      - Annual Reports, 1965-1996; 10 folders (Box 28)
      - Yearly Usage Statistics, 1983-2007 (Box 28)
      - Statistics, 1968-1972 (Box 28)
  - Michigan Historical Collections, 1919-2014; 1935-2014
    The Michigan Historical Collections series (1919-2014, bulk 1935-2014, 9.5 linear feet and one oversize box) consists of seven subseries: Office Diaries; Field Program; Topical Files; Reports; Thomas Powers' Talks; Len Coombs's files; and Lost, Recataloged, Discarded or Transferred Materials. A long run of Office Diaries (2 linear feet) covers the years 1935-1963.
    - Office Diaries
      Early on, the diaries were relatively informative documents, often including entries describing visitors and events at the BHL. Increasingly, however, they became more like logbooks recording commonplace transactions, such as the number of letters prepared each day and the name of each letter's recipient.
      - 1935-1949, 15 volumes (Box 29)
      - 1950-1963, 12 volumes (Box 30)
    - Field Program
      The Field Program subseries, 1937-2002 (2 linear feet) begins with "trip reports" written between 1935 and 1985. A trip report is a written summary of a contact by a BHL staff member and a donor or potential donor of material. The subseries also includes "Donor Lead Sheets" for the period 1988 and 1995 which are arranged alphabetically and contain information regarding the pursuit of specific collections; and "Donor Lead Card Catalog" for the period 1960s-2000s with names, addresses, and field notes, also arranged alphabetically, located in an oversize box.
      - Trip Reports, 1937-1986; 38 folders (Box 31)
      - Trip Report Indices, 1937-1985 (Box 32)
        - 1937-1940 (Box 32)
        - 1948-1957 (Box 32)
        - 1958-1960 (Box 32)
        - 1961-1963 (Box 32)
        - 1964-1966 (Box 32)
        - 1967-1969 (Box 32)
        - 1970-1972 (Box 32)
        - 1973-1975 (Box 32)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 32)
        - 1979-1981 (Box 32)
        - 1982-1984 (Box 32)
        - 1985 (Box 32)
      - Librarian/Cataloger Reports
        The Librarian/Cataloger Reports (0.2 linear feet) consists of reports filed by various individuals who held this position between 1955 and 1980. The Collections Committee was formed in 1992, and this subseries contains the committee's agendas and meeting summaries. This series also contains two folders of excerpts from the Regents Proceedings that reference the Michigan Historical Collections and the Bentley Library.
        - MHC Cataloger Reports, 1952-1964 (Box 32)
        - MHC Cataloger Monthly Reports, 1955-1969 (Box 32)
        - MHC Cataloger Monthly Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 32)
        - Librarian Reports, Ida C. Brown, 1955-1968 (Box 32)
        - Librarian's Reports, S. F. Steel, 1974-1980 (Box 32)
      - Monthly Work Reports, 1961-1987; 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Proposed Collecting Projects (Marshall, Michigan), circa 1968 (Box 32)
      - MHC in the Regents Proceedings, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - State of Michigan House Resolution No.275 for commemorating the 50th Anniversary of the Founding of the Michigan Historical Collections, 1985 (Map-case 3)
      - Archival Literature, 1993 (Box 33)
      - Collections Committee agendas, reports, and background research by meeting date, 1992-2002; 24 folders (Box 33)
      - Donor Lead Sheets A-Z (by donor name), 1988-1995; 4 folders (Box 33)
      - Forms, 1983-1988 (Box 33)
      - Miscellaneous, 1995-1998 (Box 33)
      - Outreach, 1992-1993 (Box 33)
      - Retreat, 1986 (Box 33)
    - Topical Files
      The Topical Files subseries (1980-2009, 1.7 linear feet) includes files that were contributed by Leonard Coombs, Marilyn McLaughlin, Thomas Powers, Ken Scheffel and others. It includes materials related to the development of the access and description systems employed by the Bentley, as well an interesting "Introduction to MHC Manual," created around 1980.
      - ALEPH Bibliographic Records Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 65)
      - ALEPH Cataloging Manual, 2004 (Box 65)
      - ALEPH for Archives, 2004-2005 (Box 65)
      - Authorities Library Management System (LMS), 2004-2006; 3 folders (Box 65)
      - Bentley Image Bank Development, 2000-2003 (Box 65)
      - Best of the Bentley / Visual Resources Online, 1998-1999 (Box 65)
      - Black Churches Project
        - Bethel African Methodist Episcopal (A.M.E.), Saginaw, 1977-1984 (Box 75)
        - Calvary Baptist, 1988-1993 (Box 75)
        - Little Rock Baptist, 1988 (Box 75)
        - Metropolitan Baptist, 1987-1988
        - Peace Baptist, 1987-1997 (Box 75)
        - People's Community Church, 1988-1997 (Box 75)
        - Plymouth Congregational, 1987-1988 (Box 75)
        - St. John's Presbyterian, 1989 (Box 75)
        - St. Stephen African Methodist Episcopal (A.M.E.), 1990 (Box 75)
        - Black Churches Background, 1988-1994; 2 folders (Box 75)
        - General project info, undated (Box 75)
      - Chinese seminars, 1999-2001 (Box 65)
      - County Histories Digitization, 2004-2008 (Box 65)
      - Field database, undated (Box 65)
      - Field program: Ken Scheffel, 1973-1986 (Box 65)
      - Google digitization project, 2001-2009 (Box 65)
      - Introduction to MHC Manual, 1980 (Box 65)
      - McLaughlin, Marilyn -- Audio archivist, 1990-1993 (Box 65)
      - Metadata, Description and Records Committee, 2005-2008; 5 folders (Box 65)
      - Michigan Newspaper Project, 1984 (Box 66)
      - Michigan Newspaper Project, 1994-2007; 2 folders (Box 66)
      - Michigan Newspaper Project Proposal, 1992 (Box 66)
      - MIRLYN, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 66)
      - MIRLYN Post-load, 1994-2000 (Box 66)
      - MIRLYN Statistics, 1996-2004 (Box 66)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) Newspaper Project, 2004-2006 (Box 66)
      - Newspaper exhibit, 2006 (Box 66)
      - Polar Bear digitization, 2002-2005 (Box 66)
      - Polar Bear replacement planning, 2009 (Box 66)
      - Polar Bear Vlad Signorelli Study, 1992 (Box 66)
      - Polar Bear Yakel Website, 2007-2009 (Box 66)
      - Pre-catalog archival management system, 1990
      - Selections from Sorting room wall, undated (Box 76)
      - Vatican OCLC, 2010-2012 (Box 66)
      - VuFind Group Indexes and Facets, 2008 (Box 66)
      - Weideman, Chris: Talk on Bentley Fieldwork, 1990 (Box 66)
    - Reports
      The Reports subseries (1969-2012, 0.8 linear feet) includes narrative and statistical reports related to the activities of the division including the field program, cataloging and description, and maintenance of the visual materials in the collections.
      - Collections Division Annual Reports Statistics, 1978-2012 (Box 66)
      - Collections Division Monthly Reports, 1969-1984 (Box 66)
      - Collections Division Quarterly Reports, 1985-2012 (Box 66)
      - Field Program: Ken Scheffel Annual Reports and miscellaneous, 1980-2001 (Box 66)
      - Field Program Monthly Reports: Len Coombs, 2003-2011; 6 folders (Box 66)
      - Field Program Monthly Reports: Len Coombs, 2009-2011; 3 folders (Box 67)
      - Field Program Quarterly Reports, 1981-2002 (Box 67)
      - Librarian's Annual Report, 1981-1987 (Box 67)
      - Librarian's Annual Report, 1994-1996 (Box 67)
      - Librarian's Monthly Report, 1981-2002 (Box 67)
      - Photography and Audio-visual Annual Report, 1975-1983 (Box 67)
      - Photography and Audio-visual Bi-monthly Report, 1972-1984; 2 folders (Box 67)
      - Staff meeting reports: Tom Powers, 1977-2005 (Box 67)
    - Thomas Powers' Talks
      Thomas Powers joined the Bentley's staff in 1968 as a manuscript curator and came to supervise the arrangement and description of manuscript collections at the library. After the creation of the University Archives and Records Division in 1979, Powers headed the Michigan Historical Collections Division until his retirement in 2012.
      The Thomas Powers Talks subseries, (1976-2003, 0.2 linear feet) includes speaking notes for approximately 23 presentations.
      - 30-Year Celebration Bulletin, 1995 (Box 67)
      - 50th Anniversary of the Bentley, 1987 (Box 67)
      - Appraisal at MHC, Mellon Fellows, 1983 (Box 67)
      - Archival Management for Historical Societies, Historical Society of Michigan, 1984 (Box 67)
      - Archival Practicum, International Council on Archives, 1999 (Box 67)
      - Arrangement and Description, Association of Catholic Diocesan Archivists, 1984 (Box 67)
      - Church and Denominational Collections at MHC, Archivists of Catholic Orders, 1986 (Box 67)
      - Detroit Historical Resources, Detroit Free Press, 1999 (Box 67)
      - Discussion and Comments, Michigan: Promise and Performance (50th Anniversary), 1985 (Box 67)
      - Documenting Music and the University of Michigan, Friends Meeting, 1984 (Box 67)
      - French materials at MHC, French Librarians, 1997 (Box 67)
      - Manuscripts and Archives, Libraries and Local History Workshop, 1975 (Box 67)
      - Manuscripts and Printed Materials Processing and Retrieval, Michigan Archives Association, 1976 (Box 67)
      - Marjorie Merriwether Post Papers, Friends Meeting, 1991 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Bell Photos, Michigan Bell Pioneers, 2002 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Historical Collections, Daughters of the American Revolution, undated (Box 67)
      - Michigan on the March, Friends Meeting, undated (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous, 1972-1998 (Box 67)
      - Opening of the Rev. Charles A. Hill and Hartford Memorial Baptist Papers, 2000 (Box 67)
      - Presentation to staff of Carl Levin, 2003 (Box 67)
      - Processing for Reference, Michigan Archives Association, 1989 (Box 67)
      - Stamps, Ann Arbor Stamp Club, 1998 (Box 67)
      - Tour script, undated (Box 67)
    - Len Coombs's Files
      Len Coombs joined the Bentley staff in 1981 as curator of printed works and specialized in cataloging, printed works, and maps. From 2002 until his retirement in 2014, he served as the acquisitions archivist for the Michigan Historical Collections.
      The Len Coombs's files subseries (1919-2014, bulk 1967-2014, 4 linear feet) includes speaking notes for presentations, published articles and bibliographies, exhibit materials, and materials related to the development of access and description systems used at the Bentley, related content for which can be found in the Topical Files subseries.
      - Administrative Committee, 2012-2013 (Box 79)
        [Executive records restricted until July 01, 2033 ]
      - Aeon Software, 2009-2013 (Box 72)
      - Aleph Version 20, 2010 (Box 72)
      - Annual Reports, 1977-2014 (Box 72)
      - Appraisal Type Letters, 1974-1997 (Box 72)
      - Arab American Digitizing, 2003 (Box 72)
      - Archives Courses (Box 72)
        - Cataloging, 1988 (Box 72)
        - Maps, 1990-1993; undated (Box 72)
        - MARC, 1991-2001 (Box 72)
        - Non-Manuscript Material, 1994 undated (Box 72)
        - Photos, 1987-1993; undated (Box 72)
        - Practicum, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 72)
        - Printed Works, 1977-1985 (Box 72)
      - Artifacts, undated (Box 72)
      - Audio Project, 2013-2014 (Box 72)
      - Authorities Training, 2004 (Box 72)
      - AV Project, 2004-2012 (Box 72)
      - Bentley Stories, 2013-2014 (Box 72)
      - BHL Website, 2007-2008; undated (Box 72)
      - Bibliographies (Box 72)
        - County Atlases, circa, 1931-1970 (Box 72)
        - County Histories, 1948-1981 (Box 72)
      - Bicentennial, 2013 (Box 72)
      - Birds Eye View Digitizing, 2005-2006 (Box 72)
      - Book Reviews, 1987-1999 (Box 72)
      - Book Sale, 2010-2014 (Box 72)
      - Capital Campaign, 2013 (Box 72)
      - Cataloging (Box 72)
        - ALA Character Set, 1992 (Box 72)
        - Architectural Records, 1983-1989 (Box 72)
        - BHL w/o OCLC, undated (Box 72)
        - Conversion, 1997-1998 (Box 72)
        - Form Terms for Archival and Manuscripts Control (FTAMC) and Rare Books Genre, 1983-1993 (Box 72)
        - Framed Items, 2010 (Box 72)
        - Internet Resources, 1999-2002 (Box 72)
        - Library of Congress Authority File, 1989-1994 (Box 72)
        - Manuscripts, 1984-1994 (Box 72)
        - Mirlyn, 1989-1999; 2 folders (Box 72)
        - Miscellaneous, 1983-2011 (Box 72)
        - SGML and AACR, 1994-1997 (Box 72)
      - Civil War (Box 72)
        - General, 1961-1993 (Box 72)
        - Digitizing, 2010-2011 (Box 72)
        - Guide, 2011 undated (Box 72)
      - Cold Room, 2001-2014 (Box 73)
      - Collecting Policy, 1970-1986 (Box 73)
      - Collecting Reevaluation, 2005 (Box 73)
      - Collection Development (Box 73)
        - Natural Resources, 1986 undated (Box 73)
        - Recreation, 1986 undated (Box 73)
        - Retreat, 1992-1997 (Box 73)
        - Social Organizations, 1986 (Box 73)
      - Conservation Plan, 2013 (Box 73)
      - Contents Lists (Box 73)
        - Maps, 1968-1987 (Box 73)
        - Polar Bear Maps-U.S. Army Corps of Engineers 310th Regiment (O'Dell), undated (Box 73)
        - Richard/Monteith Libraries, undated (Box 73)
      - DACS, 2005-2006; undated (Box 73)
      - De La Vergne Collection, 1968-1992 (Box 73)
      - Desiderata Lists: County Histories, County Atlases, 1955-1988 (Box 73)
      - Detroit View ID, 1940 (Box 73)
      - Digital Archives, 2006-2011 (Box 73)
      - Digital County Histories Addition, undated
      - Digital Records, 2007-2011 (Box 73)
      - Digital Retreat, 2011 (Box 73)
      - Directories, City and County, 1964; 1997 undated (Box 73)
      - Diversity, 1998-2000 (Box 73)
      - EAD, 1998-2010 (Box 73)
      - Exchanges, 1977-1983 (Box 73)
      - Exhibits (Box 73)
        - De La Vergne Maps, 1986 (Box 73)
        - De La Vergne Selections, 2004-2005 (Box 73)
        - Detroit Transportation, 2001 (Box 73)
        - Early Ann Arbor Maps, undated (Box 73)
        - Environmentalism, 1988 (Box 73)
        - Indian Exhibit, 1989 (Box 73)
        - Indian Exhibit for League, 1989 (Box 73)
        - Life on the Great Lakes, undated (Box 73)
        - Mackinac Is, 1995 (Box 73)
        - Michigan Territory Bicentennial, 2004-2005 (Box 73)
        - Polar Bears, 1999 (Box 73)
      - Family Name Authority Problem, 2001-2011 (Box 73)
      - Field Issues, 2003 (Box 73)
      - Flat Shelving, undated (Box 73)
      - Future of MHC, 2010-2012 (Box 73)
      - Grad Library and Other UM Libraries (Box 73)
        - Books Retrospective Conversion, 1982-1993 (Box 73)
        - Collection Development Working Group, 1983-1991 (Box 73)
        - Desiderata Exchanges, 1979-1994 (Box 73)
        - Documents, 2000 undated (Box 73)
        - Graduate Library Collecting, 1975-1992 (Box 73)
        - Old Map Transfer, 1983-1984 (Box 73)
        - Rare Book Room Exchange, 1985 (Box 73)
        - WebZ, 1996-1997 (Box 73)
      - Loan to Flint, 1984-1988 (Box 74)
      - Maps (Box 74)
        - Ann Arbor, 1975 (Box 74)
        - Barnett List, undated (Box 74)
        - Bibliographies, 1967-1995 (Box 74)
        - Cataloging Rules, 1993 (Box 74)
        - Collecting/Use, 1986-1987 (Box 74)
        - Michigan Maps and Atlases in Other Libraries, 1992 (Box 74)
        - Miscellaneous, 1977-2003 (Box 74)
        - Questionnaires, 1983-2003 (Box 74)
        - Rolled (Box 74)
          - Conservation, 1981-1983 (Box 74)
          - Conservation (Kathy Rochler), 1984 (Box 74)
          - Shelf List, 1982 undated (Box 74)
        - Topo-USGS, 1985-1991; undated (Box 74)
        - Townships, undated (Box 74)
      - MARC-Field Inventory, 2003 (Box 74)
      - Meeting Notes, 1981-2013 (Box 74)
      - MHC Meeting Reports, 2003-2006 (Box 74)
      - Michigan Library Consortium (MLC) Workshop (Box 74)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 74)
        - 2004-2005 (Box 74)
      - Monthly Field Activity Reports (Box 74)
        - 2012 (Box 74)
        - 2013 (Box 74)
      - Newspapers (Box 74)
        - Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC), 1988-1992 (Box 74)
        - Graduate Library-Microfilm, undated (Box 74)
        - Microfilming, 1978-1985 (Box 74)
        - Miscellaneous, 1971-1993 (Box 74)
        - Underground, 2000-2002 (Box 74)
      - OCLC (Box 74)
        - Archives and Manuscripts Control (AMC), 1987-1994 (Box 74)
        - Miscellaneous, 1995-2012 (Box 74)
        - Record Overlay, 2006 (Box 74)
        - Research Libraries Information Network (RLIN), 1989-2006; 2 folders (Box 74)
        - Statistics, 2003-2004 (Box 74)
        - Union Listing, 1999-2000 (Box 74)
      - Offsite Storage/Space Planning, 1983-2000
      - Oral History Database, 2012 (Box 74)
      - Oversize Volumes, undated (Box 74)
      - Paintings, Pictures, Works of Art, 1989 undated (Box 74)
      - Photographers (Box 74)
        - Ann Arbor, 1976-1982; undated (Box 74)
        - Michigan, 1974 undated (Box 74)
      - Photographs
        - Bibliography, 1972-1975 (Box 74)
        - Michigan (Box 74)
        - Miscellaneous, 1971-1988 (Box 74)
        - Retreat, 1990 (Box 74)
        - Vertical File, undated (Box 74)
      - Polar Bear Issues, 2012-2013 (Box 74)
      - Policies/Procedures, 1996-2001 (Box 75)
      - Presentations
        - Acquisitions Planning, 2006 (Box 75)
          (Michigan Archival Association (MAA) Meeting)
        - Ann Arbor Train and Trolley Watchers, 2003 (Box 75)
        - Atlases, 1985 (Box 75)
          (Friends Meeting)
        - Church Records, 2006 (Box 75)
          (Local History Conference)
        - First Presbyterian Hilltoppers Senior Group, 2013 (Box 75)
        - Google Project, 2010 (Box 75)
          (MAA Meeting)
        - Houghton, Hubbard, and Higgins, 1985
          (Michigan Map Society)
        - Indian Life in Southeastern Michigan, undated (Box 75)
        - Kempf House/Friends, 2007 (Box 75)
        - Kyrza CIO Group, 2013 (Box 75)
        - Maps, undated (Box 75)
        - Maps of the 19th Century, 2000-2013 (Box 75)
        - Polar Bears, 1999 (Box 75)
          (Alumni Talk)
        - Polar Bears, 2002 (Box 75)
          (Chelsea Kiwanis Club, includes slides)
        - Polar Bears, 2009 (Box 75)
          (Grosse Pointe Rotary Club)
        - Printed Works in Archives, 1982 (Box 75)
        - Printed Works in Archives, 1981 (Box 75)
          (Midwest Archives Conference (MAC) Meeting)
        - Printed Works in Archives (Box 75)
          (Society of American Archivists (SAA) Meeting)
        - Rowfant Club and other "Treasures", 1995 (Box 75)
        - Society of Automobile Historians (SAH), 2013 (Box 75)
        - Student Life, 1989 (Box 75)
        - Transportation History, 1982 (Box 75)
        - Upper Peninsula Industry, 2002 (Box 75)
        - Vatican Archives, undated (Box 75)
        - Vatican Archives, 1989 (Box 75)
          (MAC Meeting)
      - Publications
        - "A New Access System for the Vatican Archives" (SAA), 1989 (Box 75)
        - "Halley's Comet at the University of Michigan, 1910", undated (Box 75)
        - "Michigan's Underground Press", undated (Box 75)
        - Polar Bear Bibliography Illustrations, 1919-1929; undated (Box 75)
        - Polar Bear Bibliography Printing Copy, 1988 (Box 75)
        - Underground Press in Michigan Bibliography, 1982 (Box 75)
      - Railroads, undated (Box 75)
      - Richard, Gabriel, 1985-2013 (Box 75)
      - Sanborn Map Company/OCLC, 2002 (Box 75)
      - Signal of Liberty, 2004 (Box 75)
      - Stack Tenants, 2006-2013 (Box 75)
      - Statistics, 1997 (Box 75)
      - Strategic Planning-Kardia, 2013-2014 (Box 75)
      - Subject Headings in the Card Catalog for the Michigan Alumnus and Quarterly Review, undated (Box 75)
      - Suburban Newspapers, 1989-2003 (Box 75)
      - Tapes, 2010-2011 (Box 75)
      - Transition, 2012-2013 (Box 75)
      - UARP Field, 2002-2003 (Box 75)
      - UM Headings, 1996 undated (Box 75)
      - Vertical File, 1989-1991 (Box 75)
      - Web Archiving Report, 2011-2012 (Box 75)
      - Women, 2000 undated
    - Lost, Recataloged, Discarded or Transferred Materials
      Two boxes of catalog index cards comprise the subseries, Lost, Re-cataloged, Discarded or Transferred Materials, 1949-1989 (0.6 linear feet). This assembly was largely generated during the transition from a card catalog to an online public access catalog system, when items that had been separately cataloged were returned to their collections of origin to be described collectively in finding aids, rather than through separate entries.
      - Catalog index card file arranged alphabetically by author, 1949-1989 (Box 68)
      - Catalog index card file arranged alphabetically by author, 1949-1989 (Box 68)
  - Preservation and Conservation, 1987-2004